[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M1_EnterZone_EG",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M1_EG_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "09A_M1_Flask",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Invasion of Artemis",
        "Description": "Morgaine requests your assistance to battle the Ancient Huntress Artemis and the Angry Earth in Old First Light. Collect seeds for an inoculate to enter and then work the rangers and druids of the region to assess the enemy.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It was the right thing. We had no choice.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It's often acts committed in desperation that lead to even more desperate consequences, but we console ourselves thus.\\n\\nAnd now we must arrest the Angry Earth's vengeance, else First Light is only the beginning.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Collect those seeds, young one. Artemis wastes not a moment and neither shall we.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So you've heard the ominous words of the Huntress, have you? Somehow, she sounds different, knowing she's an Ancient. \\n\\nHmph. No matter, the content of her message is the greater concern. I trust you agree.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M1_EnterZone_SM",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M1_SM_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "09A_M1_Flask",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Invasion of Artemis",
        "Description": "Morgaine requests your assistance to battle the Ancient Huntress Artemis and the Angry Earth in Old First Light. Collect seeds for an inoculate to enter and then work the rangers and druids of the region to assess the enemy.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It was the right thing. We had no choice.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It's often acts committed in desperation that lead to even more desperate consequences, but we console ourselves thus.\\n\\nAnd now we must arrest the Angry Earth's vengeance, else First Light is only the beginning.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Collect those seeds, young one. Artemis wastes not a moment and neither shall we.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So you've heard the ominous words of the Huntress, have you? Somehow, she sounds different, knowing she's an Ancient. \\n\\nHmph. No matter, the content of her message is the greater concern. I trust you agree.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M1_EnterZone_RW",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M1_RW_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "09A_M1_Flask",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Invasion of Artemis",
        "Description": "Morgaine requests your assistance to battle the Ancient Huntress Artemis and the Angry Earth in Old First Light. Collect seeds for an inoculate to enter and then work the rangers and druids of the region to assess the enemy.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It was the right thing. We had no choice.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It's often acts committed in desperation that lead to even more desperate consequences, but we console ourselves thus.\\n\\nAnd now we must arrest the Angry Earth's vengeance, else First Light is only the beginning.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Collect those seeds, young one. Artemis wastes not a moment and neither shall we.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So you've heard the ominous words of the Huntress, have you? Somehow, she sounds different, knowing she's an Ancient. \\n\\nHmph. No matter, the content of her message is the greater concern. I trust you agree.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M2_FindOakes",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M2_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "PotionFamilyWardAngryEarthT4",
        "ItemRewardQty": 10,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Into the Wilds",
        "Description": "Morgaine requests that you travel west in search of survivors and Hargest's rangers. Help whoever you can, bring back any survivors, and if possible find a means to investigate the horrors beyond the inner bramble walls.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should search for survivors.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, particularly with this revelation that Artemis may have some twisted intent for them.\\n\\nThe rangers have searched fruitlessly so far, but that is no surprise. If you wish to help them, speak to Captain Hargest.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We must discern the Huntress's full intentions, however depressing that may be.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "That was… frightening. Images of terror and evil creatures of legend... were they hallucinations? Let us hope.\\n\\nEither way, Artemis's intentions clearly go beyond the extermination of humanity. She forges a new natural order.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M3_EnterJungle",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M3_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Hargest_NE_C",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M3",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M2",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M3_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 2,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Into the Darkness",
        "Description": "Morgaine once again needs our assistance breaking through into the lowland jungles for Captain Hargest, so that we can investigate the destroyed settlement of First Light. Help Hargest and her rangers make it down safely.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“I'll work with Trahern and Hargest.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, you do that. I must consult Myrddin's tomes. Minotaurs, gorgons, massive beasts... this is unprecedented.\\n\\nHelp these bumbling fools get a foothold to the south, and learn what you can. And be quick, for hope's sake.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If the survivor's memories are to be believed, atrocities beyond imagination are under way in the old settlement.\\n\\nWe must get there, and with haste!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Luck was with us! I found a few rangers dazed by the spores, and I saw you helping one yourself… I just hope they get back to camp. \\n\\nPoking around this site, seems we might have an ally lurking around these parts.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M4_ReachSettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M4_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Riches_M5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M4",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M3",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M4_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Survivalist's Revenge",
        "Description": "Hargest thinks we should investigate Dayspring Mills on our way to the settlement, and evidence suggests that Albert Riches may be fighting back. Travel into the overgrown village and search for whatever clues you can find.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He could probably use some help.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Sure enough, and he may have a grip on the situation at the settlement.\\n\\nI've been chewing on a plan since we set out on this mission, a way we might be able to retake the settlement and free any captives.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We've got a foothold, and that's progress! Wouldn't be surprised to get a cheer when I tell everyone back at camp.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome to the settlement of First Light, or what's left of it. Constable Magistrate Riches, at your service... whatever title you prefer.\\n\\nNow you've seen for yourself what it's like out there. It's not pretty.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M5_DefendSettlement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M5_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Riches_M5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M5",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M4",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M5_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "First Light, Last Stand",
        "Description": "Albert Riches needs reinforcements! Travel northwest to Tanglesnap Hollows where Taurus disposed a chunk of the spirit shrine, destabilizing its effectiveness. It may be a longshot, but forage for ingredients to repair the shrine and correct its power to allow our allies safe passage.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"If we can restore the spirit shrine, I do.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ah, now there's smart thinking! I like it! The Huntress's pet minotaur smashed the shrine good though, sent stone work flying way out!\\n\\nBut if you can recover the stone, and mix together a little pitch, you might repair it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I have to admit, things were starting to get a little dark both outside... and inside my head at one point.\\n\\nIt's been better since you arrived. Much better.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, that was a fight for the ages! I'd say after today, we won't give the leaf lady another inch of this land! \\n\\nHuntress thinks nature's on her side, but she forgot about human nature! The good, the bad, and the vengeful!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M6_FindKim",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M6_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kim",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M6",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M5",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M6_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 2,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Abducted Artificer",
        "Description": "Survivalist Riches implores us for aid, saving his kidnapped friend Jihoon Kim. Kim was captured by Medusa in the initial invasion, but Riches recently spotted him being dragged east to Saircor, go rescue the Artificer if you can.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do you mean by 'other purposes'?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Not sure, but it didn't sound good. Jihoon Kim - the town artificer a mechanical genius - Artemis said she had a special project for Kim, and that's all I know.\\n\\nThat sweaty Minotaur knocked him flat and carried him away.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'm not the most trusting man. Artificer Kim is the best friend I have. You have to get him out of there.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Even when I heard the sounds of battle, I hardly believed it possible. I have been down here more days than I can count.\\n\\nThe things I witnessed… the things I helped create… tell me, are we too late? Have they taken over?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M7_ExtractKim",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M7_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kim_SC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M7",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M6",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M7_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Escaping The Ruins",
        "Description": "Jihoon Kim believes Medusa and Artemis stole an item of importance and stashed it at Portico Tideswallow. If the item is recovered, it may convince the Minotaur there is something sinister going on with Artemis and the Beast Lords.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"They're turning captives into hercyne?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, please don't ask for any more details. I worked on the machine for weeks, and then I saw… only the beginning.\\n\\nMedusa brought me back down to these ruins, leaving the Minotaur as my jailer.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I had given up hope of ever seeing a human face again.\\n\\nI will never forget what I have endured.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well done. You are indeed a formidable warrior, and I am deeply in your debt for my liberation.\\n\\nIt seems Aeternum is not yet overrun with hercyne, and there is yet hope.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M8_MeetTaurus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M8_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Taurus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M8",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M7",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M8_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Maze and the Minotaur",
        "Description": "Kim asks that we boldly brave the Labyrinth of the minotaur Taurus, Northeast of the Ancient ruins, so that we may speak to him. Survive the deadly challenges within, and parley with the beastman if you can.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We have to stop them somehow.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "These Beast Lords with whom Artemis has forged an alliance would seem to be the final part of her plan.\\n\\nWhatever power they bring to her cause is primal, and in exchange she promises the beasts a share in her new order.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I… am so sorry… for my hand in aiding them with that Ancient device. \\n\\nI didn't know the purpose they intended until it was too late. It must be destroyed.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So you see, I swear no allegiance to the Huntress, and I do not war with humanity, unless provoked. \\n\\nI have also recently learned of… strange rituals the gorgon Medusa stages in her guarded glade. Very strange.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M9_MeetShirzad",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M9_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Shirzad",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M9",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M8",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M9_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 2,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Lord of the Pride",
        "Description": "To forge an alliance with the Beast Lords we will first need to prove ourselves to them. Taurus suggests that we begin with the Lion Lord Shirzad to the north in Gurhaowl's Pride. Complete his challenge and gain an audience.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What would happen?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The Beast Lords are primal powers, far beyond anything you or I can imagine. If they war, they will win.\\n\\nOf equal concern, the Tear of Gaea, a relic of this island's creation safekept for millennia, but now part of the Huntress's bargain.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Shirzad will grant you audience, but be wary on approach. His pride will not tolerate trespassers.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You stood your ground with honor and fought with skill. Shirzad shall grant you an audience.\\n\\nIt will be difficult to compete with the Huntress's bargain, but we will hear your offer.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M10_MeetKurok",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M10_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kurok",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M9",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M10_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "BananaT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 5,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Proving Grounds",
        "Description": "Shirzad has listened to our plea and is willing to entertain our propositions for now. Travel west to Kurok's Anchorage and speak with the Gorilla Lord Kurok. Deliver Shirzad's message and gain an audience with the Lord.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Because she uses beasts as fodder for her new army.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "… If the Huntress seeks to trick us in this alliance, you will need no bargain, human. We will seek our own vengeance.\\n\\nBut you present no evidence to support the boldness of your accusation.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Be wary of Mahantaram; he has not been himself.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You are… no normal human. That is sure. You fought with great strength, and while you fought, I communed with Shirzad.\\n\\nYour claims against the Huntress concern me gravely, all the more because Mahantaram has spent much time with her.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M11_FightMahantaram",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M11_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_WC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M11_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "09A_M11_CraftingMatsBox",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Rage of the Mammoth",
        "Description": "Kurok has accepted our bid of peace for now, and is willing to reconvene with Shirzad over their fate on Aeternum. He now worries for his kin Mahantaram, the final Lord. Head east to the Trampled Lands, and face the mammoth.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I will go and entreat with him as well.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Go quickly, for even as we speak, I stretch out to commune with him, and Mahantaram does not respond.\\n\\nThe Mammoths have begun to rampage, and I fear something transpires beyond our awareness.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I sense strange changes within Mahantaram's soul, and I hear the thunder of his tribe resounding in the earth.\\n\\nIt may be that for the mammoths, the war has already begun.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Soulwarden! How long has it been? Much has transpired since you left, and the magic in this land swirls into a maelstrom. \\n\\nArtemis has begun some ritual at the Tower. Ready or not, the time to fight is here.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M12_FightMedusa",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M12_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Trahern_HG",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M12_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Garden of the Gorgon",
        "Description": "Morgaine entreats us to retrieve the Tear of Gaea at all costs, but first we must defeat Medusa. Taurus already makes his way to her vile gardens south west of the ranger camp. Slay the Gorgon and drive her from these lands.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I will join the Minotaur to defeat her.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Then you will need protection from her gaze unless you want to be turned to stone! And you are fortunate to have a friend like Morgaine.\\n\\nThis tincture will protect you and cure your bull-headed friend if he has acted in blind aggression.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I can only hope that Trahern and I have the magic and knowledge you will need to stop what Artemis has begun.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I do not revel in the suffering of others, but the cries of Medusa were like a fresh wind of hope. \\n\\nWe must now destroy the foul enclave where crimes against nature continue even now.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M13_AttuneStaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M13_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_SE",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M13_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Arcana Aligned",
        "Description": "Trahern and Morgaine believe they may have devised a means of capturing Artemis and securing the Tear. Meet Morgaine up the road in the high mountains of what is now Scalefang Enclave to see what magic she has in mind.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Trust Morgaine. She knows what she's doing\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I hope so. We can only sow the seeds of possibility; nature must determine whether we harvest good fortune.\\n\\nGo and seek Morgaine within the enclave. If you clear the way, I will join you shortly to do my part.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go swift and stay strong. We will need your abilities in the battle to come. \\n\\nDefeating Artemis will take great effort.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well done. What we have achieved here by siphoning these Ancient energies is very similar to what Myrddin did to first empower his Staff of Wizardry.\\n\\nBut this still falls woefully short of what is needed to battle an Ancient.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M14_GetInfusedSeed",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M14_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Morgaine_LC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M14_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 5,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "One With Nature",
        "Description": "Morgaine directs us upward to the bloom above. With our Azoth Staff now empowered by the arcane energies channeled from Elafry Pyrgo we have but one more component to secure. Fight with Trahern, claim it, and finish the spell.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So the staff will be the key.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Precisely. Unlike the Archdruid, your skills in comprehension are intact. Trahern does have a role to play however.\\n\\nArtemis twists the flora of First Light with a transformative lifeforce, and the druid can harness this.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Do not concern yourself. I am more than capable of battling my way safely to the tower.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "This goes beyond anything Myrddin ever attempted. I am proud to have assisted you. \\n\\nThe staff is but an implement, however. You will need to weaken Artemis greatly to have any chance of unleashing the staff's new potential.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_M15_FightArtemis",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_M15_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Trahern_End",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_M15_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "Artifact_Set1_MediumLegs",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The End of New Eden",
        "Description": "Morgaine puts forth her final plea - capture Artemis and secure the Tear of Gaea from her grasp. With your allies at your back, ascend Elafry Pyrgo and battle the Ancient Artemis for the fate of the region, Aeternum, and the World.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do I do with the Tear of Gaea?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Heh. That is an excellent question, and I will need to think on it, but it should not delay us now.\\n\\nCaptain Hargest will harry her forces from the ground. Trahern and I will do what we can to slow the ritual. Go.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Even if we fail, Soulwarden, I am proud of what we have accomplished together… in scholarly terms, at least.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "We have averted the ascension of an Ancient, and yet there remains more to do. I fear what could befall the Beast Lords following their affliction. \\n\\nYou should consider returning to the region, they may need further assistance.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S0_SecretoftheSpores",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S0_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Eldred",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S0",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S0_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "SporeJellyT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Secret of the Spores",
        "Description": "Master Alchemist Eadred has made a revolutionary discovery critical to the invasion. Investigate the strange spores blooming in the region and learn how you can use them to your advantage.\\n(Requires: Harvesting 100)",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I suppose you have an answer.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I believe I have devised a method to render the toxic effects beneficial to us. It requires ingredients gathered from the plants themselves. \\n\\nI’ll prepare a special flask while you gather the spore caps. They can be found in abundance west of the camp.",
        "InProgressResponse": "It seems everything in this land wants to kill us. I suppose that shouldn't be so surprising.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Look at that, you’re glowing... I jest, of course. Remember to keep your flask in tip top shape. \\n\\nMore Sandstone should enhance it and improve the elixir's capabilities. You’ll need all the help you can get out here.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S1_SaveAnimals",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S1_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Murrow_WC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "BeastSporesT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Endangered by Artemis",
        "Description": "The Druid Keira implores you to aid the wildlife native to the region. The cries of animals call out from the depths of the jungle, and she feels their fear. Do what you can to keep them from becoming food for some new monstrosity.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Can they be saved?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "If we're quick about it. I have a special connection to the wild things. Their cries… they’re coming from the south. \\n\\nFree our animal friends and purge any fiendish flora that's disturbed the natural order.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We don’t know what other horrors were spawned by the transformation of this land. Be cautious.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "All is calm now. \\n\\nThe animals sing with gratitude for their freedom. Thank you for giving them a second chance.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S3_HuntHercyne",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S3_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Vachon_WC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S3",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S3_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "A Beast No More",
        "Description": "Sebastian Vachon is pursuing a dangerous beast and needs your help finding it so he can study its origins. Follow its tracks through the region, defeat it, and bring its cerebrum back to the Druid.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you know what it is?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I can find out. \\n\\nIf you wish to help, slay the beast and bring me its brain. With that, I can divine the answer.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Some rangers claim to have encountered a creature such as this near the overgrown barrier deep within the mining town.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You have the brain? Let me examine it… \\n\\nStrange… it almost seems like two different beings. One is a stag, but the other… feels strangely familiar? It can’t be. I must inform the archdruid!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S4_BlowUpFarm",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S4_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S4",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M3",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S4_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "AngryEarthSporesT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Firing Back",
        "Description": "Albert Riches, the survivalist of First Light left behind some battle plans and a note. How did he know we would be coming? In any case, we should help. Go into Charlottesburgh and complete the Survivalist's bombastic plan.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Shouldn't leave a job half-done.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The plant-men made a home of Dayspring. Dragged townsfolk there when it started… into the pods. \\n\\nI've been planting explosives there for weeks. The barrels seem to confuse them. Collect the rest and blast those greeny gits to Hades.",
        "InProgressResponse": "There is a hastily sketched diagram of a farmhouse surrounded by explosives. \\n\\nStick figure Angry Earth are rushing towards it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Scuse me, lad. Think I got something in my eye. \\n\\n We lost a lot of good people when those leafy bastards showed. If the thorns and vines didn't get you, it was the Angry Earth. Good you arrived to give them a proper sendoff.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S5_SavePrivateer",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S5_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_James",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S5",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M4",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S5_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "A Friend in Need",
        "Description": "Another potential survivor, James Oxen, appears to have dropped a check-list of supplies. There is a crude drawing of a cave on the back. Collect the supplies, find the cave, and protect the survivors.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Seems Captain James is in trouble.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It's an extremely verbose note. The handwriting becomes increasingly hurried, ending in the bloodstained signature of a \"Captain James Oxen.\" \\n\\nOn the back is a list of supplies, and a crude map to a cave southwest of here.",
        "InProgressResponse": "It's an extremely verbose note. The handwriting becomes increasingly hurried, ending in the bloodstained signature of a \"Captain James Oxen.\" \\n\\nOn the back is a list of supplies, and a crude map to a cave southwest of here.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I'm not seeing things? I thought I'd die here on this God-forsaken island. You have my eternal thanks, mate! \\n\\nI'm getting off this rock and damn the consequences. If you've a mind to brave the Stormwall, you're always welcome in my crew.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S6_TrackBeasts",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S6_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Fionn",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S6",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M5",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S6_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Tracking the Herd",
        "Description": "The Knight-Errant Fionn hopes we can render some assistance investigating the migratory behavior of the beasts moving between the nearby territory and the northern beastlands. Follow the clues and report back.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What kind of information?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Migratory patterns to confirm they're heading for a choke point the Marauders picked out. \\n\\nI'm spent from running for my life. If you could check the coast for tracks, I would appreciate it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Travel south along the coast and try not to get spotted. \\n\\nThese beasts are just like the rest of Aeternum's wildlife - vicious and territorial.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "How was the investigation? You look like you ran into something dangerous. \\n\\nIf they're headed up north, that means they'll spring the Marauders' trap. They were bound to be right sometime. Many thanks!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S7_StopPlague",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S7_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Ramla",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S7",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M5",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S7_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "AncientSporesT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Plague for All Factions",
        "Description": "Ramla and her crew have come down with a mysterious illness. Something dangerous has awoken in these ruins and someone tough will be needed to investigate. See if you can solve the mystery.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"This island continues to surprise.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I would prefer the surprises to stop. The symptoms are nothing particularly unique, but no treatments are working. \\n\\nI know you're capable of facing whatever's out there. Finding the source could save my team.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The Syndicate are held up here instead of setting up power for the Marauders. \\n\\nThe whole project could fall apart if we don't find an answer to this blasted plague.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "An alchemist told us our \"curse\" was some Ancient defense mechanism, but I dismissed the idea until the sickness faded.  Now I owe the Syndicate up north an apology.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S8_FixAncientWiring",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S8_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Josephine",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S8_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Defective Defenses",
        "Description": "Josephine and her Syndicate specialists were ambushed when they set off some form of automated defense system within Tideswallow. Now they need someone to deal with the Ancient Guardians and finish the repairs.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Like the one you're standing next to?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Got a knack for this do you? \\n\\nIf you gather up enough Ancient scraps, maybe you can fix the pylons. Then you may need some Ancient tomes, for setting the runes. We're busy trying to keep what we have safe.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I don't mind waiting, but I can't say the same for the Marauders. \\n\\nThey know as soon as these pylons are fixed they get to have at the Ancients, and I don't want to be on the receiving end of their impatience.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "All fixed? Us too. With the pylons repaired, our expert in Ancient machinery can attempt to gain control of the defenses. \\n\\nHe’s a Marauder, so make sure his soldiers aren’t breaking the machines. We can’t afford any more repairs.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S9_HackDefenses",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S9_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Kievan",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S9",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_S7",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S9_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "PetrifiedFragmentsT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Factions United",
        "Description": "The flow of power has been restored to the Marauders at Saircor, and Keivan needs help with the final step of the operation. Fight off the Ancient Guardians and assist with the repairs so he can gain control of their defenses.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Marauders dealing with complex traps, eh?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Looks can be deceiving, da? This will not be easy, friend. You have demonstrated mastery over Ancient Guardians. Show us Marauders another performance! \\n\\nIf you help us repair this Ancient device, we will be ready to proceed.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Every moment we delay, our foes continue their relentless advance. The man-beast to the north must not be allowed to amass his armies unchecked. \\n\\nHeaven forbid the creatures from Scalefang advance across the bridge.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Haha! Run, cowards! \\n\\nThough I take great pride in Marauder victory over the Ancient Guardians, I am even more impressed by the strength of Aeternum united. We could not have done this without you and our allies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S10_FindTaurusRelics",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S10_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Marwa",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M7",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S10_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "BeastSporesT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Heart of a Beast",
        "Description": "Pinned beneath a mysterious, rusted axe lies a note - addressed to you. It asks that you hold your judgment of the fabled Minotaur until you learn his story. Collect relics lost in the labyrinth, then speak with Marwa.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "(Examine the note.)",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "“The Minotaur could be a force of wanton destruction, but he chooses not to be. He is hunted purely due to lies and falsehoods. The labyrinth contains relics that hold the truth. Bring them to me and I shall reveal his legacy.”\\n\\n-Marwa",
        "InProgressResponse": "The note instructs you to find three relics within the labyrinth and deliver them to Marwa.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Taurus… Minotaur… Enkidu... he has gone by many names. I healed him after he was attacked in Weaver’s Fen decades ago. Now we fight side by side. \\n\\nHe seeks a life undisturbed, but I fear the serpent woman has other plans for him.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S11_BeatTimeTrial",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S11_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Marwa_HHOP",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S11_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Challenge of Character",
        "Description": "Marwa Shaheen has heard of your recent exploits, and knows more trials lie ahead. She wishes to offer a challenge to bolster your resolve. Visit Marwa and complete the time trial that she has prepared.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I am always ready for a challenge.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Take this torch and light the braziers I have placed across this land. \\n\\nStart south past Saircor, then follow the course to the southern goal. The path will test your strength, agility, and cunning. Be prepared.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Your flame dwindles. \\n\\nHasten to the braziers!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Masterfully done. You have no doubt gained favor with Taurus. Here is your reward. \\n\\nReturn again to test yourself further. Maintaining this routine will keep your edge sharpened for battle. But for now, rest.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S12_TraverseLionCave",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S12_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Shirzad",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S12_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Gauntlet of Kings",
        "Description": "Shirzad believes you must increase in strength if you are to quell the rage of the tainted Beast Lords and their tribes. Return to his den at Gurhaowl's Pride and once again brave the grotto below.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"No beast or man will stop me.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Then descend once more into the caverns of my kin, and defeat any who stand in your way. Do not relent and you shall be victorious. \\n\\nProve yourself worthy to defend those in your charge!",
        "InProgressResponse": "The idle are not fit to lead.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Once again you prove yourself a mighty warrior. Perhaps you have the soul of a lion? \\n\\nYou have my boon, human. Be welcome in my domain.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S13_FightLizardAvatar",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S13_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Barug",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S13_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Battle of the Beasts",
        "Description": "Barug of the Gorillas now stands in Kurok's stead, but without their Lord the tribe is in grave danger. Rally your fellow warriors to help the Gorilla tribe fight off an incursion by a champion of the Lizard Lord.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I will conquer the beast.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "With most of our allied Lords sequestered in the cavern, our tribe remains in great danger. \\n\\nFight Gazsala in the bay. Fight with everything you have.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I struggle to maintain order in Nyhart's without Kurok. \\n\\nIf Sirrussu spreads his malign influence here, others of their kind will surely invade.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "My thanks, human. I offer you our boon. \\n\\nWe weep for the Lords that are lost, and hope they may return to us in time. We need their guidance now more than ever.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S14_FightEliteBeasts",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S14_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Manmosu_SD",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S14_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Tribunal Highmound",
        "Description": "Manmosu, the new matriarch of the mammoth tribe, has taken refuge in a cave near the Tribunal Highmound to prepare for battle. Speak with her, and then prepare to assault the Highmound and its leaders.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Then we need to hurry.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You think as I do, human. Focus on eliminating the leaders. Their contagion spreads quickly if they are left to prowl. \\n\\nDo this, and you will  stop it long enough for us to deal with the greater threat within the Savage Divide.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Maintain dominance or this land will dominate you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Impressive. I wish more within the herd had your conviction. It’s time to face the Lords within their new domain. \\n\\nI grieve that it has come to this, but… they can be allowed to disrupt the primal flow no longer.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S15_ResearchDarkMagic",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S15_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Johannes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S15_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "UnpetrifiedFleshT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Medusa's Monstrosities",
        "Description": "Johannes Metzger needs assistance investigating the sinister magic Medusa had been channeling in Scalefang Enclave. Reach out to the rogue scientist, help him gather samples, and work with the mysterious technology there.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do you mean by samples?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Limbs. Guts. Brains. What else? You've skinned a deer before, yes? It's like that, but keep the bits you'd throw out. \\n\\nI just need a few more of each, then we can move on to the next phase. Do this and I'll mention you in the treatise I'm authoring!",
        "InProgressResponse": "You will not find the Hercyne by nettling me further, assistant. \\n\\nGet moving!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You have an uncanny aptitude for dissection. These samples are perfect! By studying these component parts I'll learn the intricacies of merging with Angry Earth. \\n\\nReturn when you're ready and we'll investigate Hercyne memory loss.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S16_DestroyAbomination",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S16_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Johannes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S16_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "PetrifiedFragmentsT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Medusa's Magic",
        "Description": "Johannes Metzger has even grander ambitions. Too grand to accomplish alone. Find him in the dark village and Help him with his final tasks, and he promises to share part of the credit for whatever he learns.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm as ready as I'll ever be.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That's the spirit! There are pylons like mine scattered around Scalefang Enclave. \\n\\nIf you modify them to my exact specifications, no one will notice the slight decrease in power. But we will have access to Medusa's streams of magic!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Hop to, assistant! You know what they say about idle hands…",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "My Syndicate cluster warned me not to rush progress… I believe I understand now. \\n\\nIt was presumptuous of me to assume a Hercyne with human memories could maintain mental stability. My thanks. Your services are no longer required.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S17_EstablishDefenses",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S17_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Hargest_LC",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S17_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "AngryEarthSporesT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 20,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Siege of Light's Crown",
        "Description": "Ranger-Captain Hargest has advanced into inner Light's Crown to establish a perimeter, but she needs assistance. Help the rangers restock their munitions, bolster their defenses, and fend off attacks.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"On it!\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "We can use these barricades to create a choke point. We need to funnel the enemy into cannon range.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Once this cannon is operational, we will dominate the battlefield.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Excellent work! We've got a much stronger foothold here now. Your quick thinking saved the day.  \\n\\nThis new position should discourage hostile movement through the region.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S18_ScanElafryMagic",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S18_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Gauss",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S18_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 4,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Essence of Evil",
        "Description": "Heinrich Gauss has been dispatched to investigate the dark energy pouring out of Elafry Pyrgo and assess its potential danger to the humans of Aeternum. Help him to gather samples using his proprietary capture devices.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll capture it for you.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You are far better equipped for the job… Take my latest creation with you. \\n\\nPlace it in energy rich regions atop the tower and buy some time for it to capture the storm's essence. Be careful. The power will coalesce around it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You mustn't linger long. I want to capture the storm's full ferocity.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Were you successful in collecting the… you look like you’ve seen a ghost. \\n\\nWhat happened up there?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S19_DestroyBadPlants",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S19_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Trahern_SD",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_S14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S19_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 10,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Containing the Contagion (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Archdruid Trahern has been hard at work researching methods for combating the magical plants spreading throughout the Savage Divide. He needs your assistance planting his newly created seeds within the depths of the cavern.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How does that help?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "We use Medusa’s magic against her. These seeds will absorb the taint and purify it before bursting into pristine flora. \\n\\nSimply place them where the contagion is most concentrated and allow nature to take its course.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Be careful, there are many infected creatures inside the cavern. \\n\\nIf at all possible, try to give them a swift end. They've already suffered enough.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I’m glad you made it back safely. The seeds should prevent new infections from spreading. \\n\\nI hope our paths cross again… under less dire circumstances. May the wilds always guide you, friend.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S20_DefeatBeastLords",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S20_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_Manmosu_SD",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_S14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S20_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Savage Divide (Expedition)",
        "Description": "The time has come to face the Beast Lords lost within the Savage Divide. Manmosu asks that we act as her champion, lest she risk infection by going herself. Gather your greatest allies, descend into the Divide, and defeat the Lords.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Leave him to me.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Unfortunately, he isn’t the only Beast Lord within the depths of the Highmound Caverns. The gorilla lord Kurok is inside as well. \\n\\nI’d die protecting my herd, but I fear contracting their disease.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Stay vigilant. \\n\\nYou may have defeated Mahantaram before, but the foulness festering within him makes him unpredictable.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I can feel his grip weakening on the herd. With time, the power he holds over us will diminish. \\n\\nIt still shocks me to fight alongside a human, but you have proven yourself a priceless ally. You have my gratitude.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "09A_S21_AmongStatues",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": null,
        "CanBeShared": null,
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "09A_S21_Container_Main",
        "NpcDestinationId": "09a_EdithShackleton_end",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "09A_S8",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "09A_M11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "09A_S21_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Among the Statues",
        "Description": "Dame Edith Henrietta Shackleton has gotten herself into a bit of a situation in the maze. She requires help acquiring antiquities that have been turned to stone.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why aren't you stone?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm no dunce. I studied the Classics, and have an encyclopedic knowledge of mythology. \\n\\nWhile I may have been surprised to see it was real, I know how to use a hand mirror. But I could use some help.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Have you recovered those artifacts yet? I'm getting tired from holding this position.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Splendid work! Just splendid! Imagine, this vase, if it hasn't been turned to stone, would have been as fragile as an eggshell. \\n\\nNow I can study the intricate design without fear of it shattering. Or Bloodgood's bumbling.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "",
        "Description": "",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "",
        "Description": "",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 9,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "",
        "Description": "",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
